<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Supervision on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/Supervision/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Supervision on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/Supervision/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Supervision</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/02_Supervise_team_CGC_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/02_Supervise_team_CGC_2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EC1.2 You are supervising a team of 4 technicians.  One is a brand new hire, one has only been on the team for one year, one has been on the team for 10 years and has been underperforming for the past 2 years, and the remaining technician (on the team for 10 years) is consistently exceeding expectations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning, organizing, and coordinating</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/04_Planning_CGC_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/04_Planning_CGC_2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EC3.1 Describe one of your team&amp;rsquo;s largest or most important projects or activities and how you managed it, from start to finish.  Use a project or activity where others were doing the work, but you were overseeing it.  (Maximum 500 words.) [10 marks]
–	What was the vision for this project/activity?
–	What was the outcome?  How do you know this was the outcome?
–	What was your role in reaching that outcome?
–	Looking back, what would you have done differently?  Why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please provide the contact information for someone that can corroborate your response.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Supervisor Interview Q&amp;A</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/25_supervisor_interview_QA/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/25_supervisor_interview_QA/</guid>
      <description>What characterize a great supervisor? #  A great supervisor can motivate their subordinates, they go by example, they have good observation skills, and they can utilize the strengths of the people they lead in their teams. Alternatively you can say that great supervisor maintains the highest possible productivity and motivation of the team (or of each team member), and helps the company to achieve their goals on an ongoing basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Did You Lead A Team?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Supervise_a_team/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Supervise_a_team/</guid>
      <description>A Leader&amp;rsquo;s Character #  What it is? #  a) Care about people
i) care about each and every one
example: recognize a technologist performance
ii) care about the team
example: none
b) Be patient
be patient in handling conflicts. Conflict resolution requires actions from both sides.
be patient in improving performance. Would take more years to get there.
c) Not give up could be frustrated when helping difficult people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Are You The Best Fit For Supervisor?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Why_is_the_best_fit_for_supervisor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Why_is_the_best_fit_for_supervisor/</guid>
      <description>My strength #  My strength: Commitment to team success (1), organization/plan, monitoring, deliver constructive feedback, build up others, build trust in relationship, hold myself accountable for mistakes rather than blame team members.
My experience #  Experience in supervision in unionized environment.
Experience in planning, assigning tasks, monitoring performance.
Experience in motivation,
Misc. #  CGC: Chemist [2022.06]
Chalk River: Dosimetry second head [2016.09]
Koch: Lab manager [2018.06]
  Commitment to team success: run the business as if it is my business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deal with a Difficult Employee</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Difficult_people_tip_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Difficult_people_tip_01/</guid>
      <description>Q: Tell me about a time you had to deal with a difficult employee
Difficult people are an inevitable part of life – and as a manager, your ability to deal with them in the right way is extra important.
You’d be surprised at the amount of useful skills you can demonstrate in answering this question well – as long as you adequately describe the resolution (and its impact), as well as the problem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
