<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ice breaking on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/ice-breaking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ice breaking on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/ice-breaking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ice Breaking</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Ice_breaking_NAIT/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Ice_breaking_NAIT/</guid>
      <description>This is kind of one of our icebreaker questions, but to just to get a little bit of more of a feel for you. We have an inside running joke in our group about Star Wars. And we were wondering if you could compare your personality and your career to any character in the whole Star Wars universe. Who would it be and why?
Well, I just watched a couple ofthe Star Wars series the movies in the Star War.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Method Development</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Method_development_NAIT/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Method_development_NAIT/</guid>
      <description>Q: Do you have any experience with method development?
A: I have two kinds of scenarios on method development. So one, one kind of scenario is when I worked in AECL, we do the analysis for the volatile organic compound and that is in the environmental samples, and we just follow the standard method. So and also tweaked a little bit based on our what we have of the instrument. So, that is very simple and quick method development that does the process is that open up open a Standard Method and follow the procedures and also there is another protocols that what is what are the parameters, we have to we have to focus on for the massive development and the massive validation, such as precision, precision accuracy, and the bias, and also robot robust, how robustness of the method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Are You Interested in Applying for This Job</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Tell_me_about_yourself_NAIT_2nd_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Tell_me_about_yourself_NAIT_2nd_interview/</guid>
      <description>a little bit about yourself and why are excited about working with the clean technologies team and why you think you would be a good fit for the team?
in a nutshell that I have the versatile skills and broad experience in different industrial applications. I will say that my interest in instrumentations applications and experience in the quality lab laboratory quality management and also I also have a interest interested in the data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greeting</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Greeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Greeting/</guid>
      <description>Ice-breaking
今天Kevin YIP 跟我做了一个mocking interview。他对我的帮助比Garth和Tony的要更贴近我一些，还是我和Kevin个性比较接近吧。
开场破冰要显得自然些。
This interview will start at 7:30am. I would say something like: Thanks for inviting an interview with you in the early morning. &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; does not mean &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; to me. I am an early person. It does not bother me at all.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
