<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Non-technical questions on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/Non-technical-questions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Non-technical questions on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/Non-technical-questions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What do you know about Our Business?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/03-Gordon-Foundation/01-Interview-Prep/Know_your_business_Gordon_prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/03-Gordon-Foundation/01-Interview-Prep/Know_your_business_Gordon_prep/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Foundation is a charitable organization. Gordon Foundation initiated DataStream program. The goal is to share the data. In order to do that, data must be standardized, verified, to comply with an observation-level data schema (standard) based on WQX standard (It was designed to enable multiple monitoring entities to share results in a common format).
DataStream was first piloted in the Mackenzie Basin with the support and collaboration of the Government of the Northwest Territories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges You Would Face</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Challenges_NAIT/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Challenges_NAIT/</guid>
      <description>If you were the successful candidate, what do you think some of the challenges you would face? Yeah. What kind of challenges do you think you would face with our group? Or in our group?
my understanding from the newcomers, perspective, is that to understand the dynamic of the team, the first the first priority, is to find out that how everybody is everybody&amp;rsquo;s work together. And then what is the what the what is everybody&amp;rsquo;s strengths?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strength and Weakness</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/03-Gordon-Foundation/01-Interview-Prep/Strength_N_Weakness_Gordon_prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/03-Gordon-Foundation/01-Interview-Prep/Strength_N_Weakness_Gordon_prep/</guid>
      <description>Strength: technical savvy.
Weakness:
 there are still lots to learn. Learn programming codes on the job. had few presentation opportunities at work, but practiced the skillset at Toastmasters. syllable missing.
   I have done a self-assessment for data scientists and data analysts.
Strength:
 I am a good listener. I am focused on getting tangible business results with data. no problem of talking in front of a group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strength and Weakness</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/04-Sysmex/First-Interview/Strength_N_Weakness_Sysmex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/04-Sysmex/First-Interview/Strength_N_Weakness_Sysmex/</guid>
      <description>What would you say are your strengths and weaknesses?
Syllables</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do you know about Our Business?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/04-Sysmex/Interview-Prep/Know_your_business_Sysmex_2nd_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/04-Sysmex/Interview-Prep/Know_your_business_Sysmex_2nd_interview/</guid>
      <description>Knowledge about Sysmex products #  Hematology analyzer for large and small labs. blood coagulation analyzer - Hemostasis.
Urinalysis analyzer Flow cytometry Informatics solutions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do you know about Our Business?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Know_your_business_NAIT/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Know_your_business_NAIT/</guid>
      <description>what do you know about our group and the work that we do? I think you&amp;rsquo;ve, you&amp;rsquo;ve kind of touched on it a little bit, but if you could just like explain it, in your own words.
They&amp;rsquo;re there, that some research areas, for instance, the PRIA, and then re re, kind of the sort of how to show say that material characterization and site remediation. Is overall that also the different industries that are oil, or gas and industry and food, so he sets up the full size, then to understand the the protein profile in some plant?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
