<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Troubleshooting on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/Troubleshooting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Troubleshooting on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/Troubleshooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thinking Things Through</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Think_through_healthcanada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Think_through_healthcanada/</guid>
      <description>[Location: Health_Canada_interview-3, 39:39]
DEFINITION
Advise and plan based on analysis of issues and trends, and how these link to the responsibilities, capabilities, and potential of the organization. Scan an ever-changing, complex environment in anticipation of emerging crises and opportunities. Develop well-informed advice and strategies that are sensitive to the various needs of multiple stakeholders and partners, reflect the strategic direction, and position the organization for success.
QUESTIONS Being able to identify and solve problems is an important aspect of being a Chemist II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hands-on Experience</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/02-Working-Situations/05-LifeLabs/04_Hands-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/02-Working-Situations/05-LifeLabs/04_Hands-on/</guid>
      <description>Back pressure correction #  There was a time at LifeLabs. The back pressure of a LC-MS/MS was built up over 600 bar. The instrument stopped because the back pressure went up above the limit. I disconnected the UHPLC column from the mass spectrometer. Observed the back pressure reading. The back pressure was still high, so I disconnected the UHPLC column from the guard column. The back pressure dropped. I knew the problem was in the UHPLC column.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
