<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Toastmasters on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/Toastmasters/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Toastmasters on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/Toastmasters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mastering the Laugh</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/03_mastering_the_laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/03_mastering_the_laugh/</guid>
      <description>Mastering the Laugh #  Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, humor is hard! Toastmasters helps us overcome stage fright, speak to strangers and think on our feet. We&amp;rsquo;re adept at speaking to inform, persuading our audiences and touching them with inspirational tales of love and loss. But how do we &amp;ldquo;break a leg&amp;rdquo; (a good thing in comedy parlance) by tickling our audiences&#39; &amp;ldquo;funny bones&amp;rdquo;?
Speeches employing humor are better received; audiences are more receptive when they&amp;rsquo;ve laughed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humor to the Rescue</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/04_humor_to_the_rescue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/04_humor_to_the_rescue/</guid>
      <description>A witty response is good for business.
For a leader who&amp;rsquo;s building social and business relationships, humor is a wonderful tool. People want to associate with leaders who have a positive personality and a sense of humor. When you are skilled at using humor, it increases trust and likeability. It builds, and sometimes even rescues, relationships. It clearly strengthens your leadership skills. As a significant fringe benefit, a sense of humor gives you a better-tuned humor radar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acceptable Humor: The Mark of a Professional</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/11_acceptable_humor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/11_acceptable_humor/</guid>
      <description>How to navigate the minefield of good and bad taste.
At a recent Table Topics session, our Topicsmaster quoted a news clipping about someone who grafted an ear to his forehead in the name of art. A member responded: &amp;ldquo;We were asked if an ear grafted to the forehead was art. Technically, it&amp;rsquo;s called Forehead Art&amp;hellip;or F-ART. Which gives you my answer to whether or not it&amp;rsquo;s art.&amp;rdquo;
Oops. That joke crossed the invisible line separating appropriate humor from the inappropriate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
