<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interview Preparation on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Interview-Prep/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interview Preparation on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Interview-Prep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tell Me About Yourself</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Interview-Prep/Tell_me_about_yourself_NAIT_prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Interview-Prep/Tell_me_about_yourself_NAIT_prep/</guid>
      <description>My field of study in university is Chemistry, in graduate school my study is polymer chemistry. I used gel permeation chromatography (GPC), Differential Scanning Calorimetry (DSC) and Thermal Gravimetric Analysis (TGA) to study characterization of polymer materials.
After graduation, I developed skills and experience in chemical analysis and lab accreditation in Total and SGS in China since year 2000.
We immigrated to Canada in 2004. I worked at Testmark environmental labs to provide accredited analysis for environmental monitoring and drinking water quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Questions</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Interview-Prep/Interview-Questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Interview-Prep/Interview-Questions/</guid>
      <description>First Interview #  Interview Questions Prepared #   Tell me about yourself My field of study in university is Chemistry, in graduate school my study is polymer chemistry. I used gel permeation chromatography (GPC), Differential Scanning Calorimetry (DSC) and Thermalgravimetric Analysis (TGA) to study characterization of polymer materials.  After graduation, I developed skills and experience in chemical analysis and lab accreditation in Total and SGS in China since year 2000.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
