<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>follow-up interview on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/follow-up-interview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in follow-up interview on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/follow-up-interview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are You Interested in Running ICP-OES?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Are_you_interested_in_NAIT_2nd_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Are_you_interested_in_NAIT_2nd_interview/</guid>
      <description>Review note: My answer was not solid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges You Would Face</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Challenges_NAIT/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Challenges_NAIT/</guid>
      <description>If you were the successful candidate, what do you think some of the challenges you would face? Yeah. What kind of challenges do you think you would face with our group? Or in our group?
my understanding from the newcomers, perspective, is that to understand the dynamic of the team, the first the first priority, is to find out that how everybody is everybody&amp;rsquo;s work together. And then what is the what the what is everybody&amp;rsquo;s strengths?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Breaking</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Ice_breaking_NAIT/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Ice_breaking_NAIT/</guid>
      <description>This is kind of one of our icebreaker questions, but to just to get a little bit of more of a feel for you. We have an inside running joke in our group about Star Wars. And we were wondering if you could compare your personality and your career to any character in the whole Star Wars universe. Who would it be and why?
Well, I just watched a couple ofthe Star Wars series the movies in the Star War.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instrumentation</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Instrumentation_NAIT/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Instrumentation_NAIT/</guid>
      <description>Q: are you familiar with like GCMS, ICP-OES, GPC, and TGA?
A: in my graduate school, I use TGA and DSC for polymers identifications, and to measure the physical properties. And also the other instrument, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure that say if you want to use a recyclable plastic and put it into the mix up with the new polymer materials, then probably you would want it to test the different parameters like the like the intensities and strength, those are physical parameters and property you would if you want to do the recipes of the polymers, probably you have a different instrument and to measure to measure the physical properties and measure other such as the the additives to the parliament&amp;rsquo;s So, I have an experience using those instruments, when I work in the industry, and for the GC and those instruments, I had experience hands on experience in in different lab settings, I use T&amp;rsquo;s GCMS, and the LC MS and even LC triple quard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Method Development</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Method_development_NAIT/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Method_development_NAIT/</guid>
      <description>Q: Do you have any experience with method development?
A: I have two kinds of scenarios on method development. So one, one kind of scenario is when I worked in AECL, we do the analysis for the volatile organic compound and that is in the environmental samples, and we just follow the standard method. So and also tweaked a little bit based on our what we have of the instrument. So, that is very simple and quick method development that does the process is that open up open a Standard Method and follow the procedures and also there is another protocols that what is what are the parameters, we have to we have to focus on for the massive development and the massive validation, such as precision, precision accuracy, and the bias, and also robot robust, how robustness of the method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do you know about Our Business?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Know_your_business_NAIT/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Know_your_business_NAIT/</guid>
      <description>what do you know about our group and the work that we do? I think you&amp;rsquo;ve, you&amp;rsquo;ve kind of touched on it a little bit, but if you could just like explain it, in your own words.
They&amp;rsquo;re there, that some research areas, for instance, the PRIA, and then re re, kind of the sort of how to show say that material characterization and site remediation. Is overall that also the different industries that are oil, or gas and industry and food, so he sets up the full size, then to understand the the protein profile in some plant?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Are You Interested in Applying for This Job</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Tell_me_about_yourself_NAIT_2nd_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/05-NAIT/Second-Interview/Tell_me_about_yourself_NAIT_2nd_interview/</guid>
      <description>a little bit about yourself and why are excited about working with the clean technologies team and why you think you would be a good fit for the team?
in a nutshell that I have the versatile skills and broad experience in different industrial applications. I will say that my interest in instrumentations applications and experience in the quality lab laboratory quality management and also I also have a interest interested in the data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are Challenges or Adjustments for Us</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Challenges_from_my_perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Challenges_from_my_perspective/</guid>
      <description>Q: Describe what you foresee to be as challenges or adjustments for us in this new role?
A: team dynamics, learn to run new instrument, teaching,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
