<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Relationship Management on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/Relationship-Management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Relationship Management on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/Relationship-Management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Effective Interpersonal Skills</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Interpersonal_skills_healthcanada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Interpersonal_skills_healthcanada/</guid>
      <description>DEFINITION
Works collaboratively with others, readily shares information, knowledge and personal strengths, and seeks to understand and the perspectives of others to achieve common goals.
QUESTIONS
We must often work as a team to get a task done and sometimes the members of that team differ from us in temperament or in the way they work. Tell us about a recent experience in which you were part of team and had to adapt to working with someone despite your differences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approach to Client</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/04-Sysmex/First-Interview/Approach_client/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/04-Sysmex/First-Interview/Approach_client/</guid>
      <description>What are your approaches let&amp;rsquo;s say you&amp;rsquo;re visiting a new client it&amp;rsquo;s important to be able to establish the trust with them? How would you kind of approach meeting a new a new customer or client?
[listen to the customer and get a good understanding of what the issue is. So that&amp;rsquo;s that&amp;rsquo;s one important aspect of the role being a good listener.]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disagree With Your Supervisor</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Disagree_with_supervisor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Disagree_with_supervisor/</guid>
      <description>Q: What are some of the things you and your supervisor have disagreed on?
Situation #1: in hiring a quality officer
Disagree on:
I: poor qualification
Supervisor: better personality
Consequence: I respected my supervisor. It turned out a good hire.
Situation #2: Safety moment in the meeting
Disagree with safety practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relationship Management Questions</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Relationship_management_questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Relationship_management_questions/</guid>
      <description>Source: Relationship Management
Collaboration and Interpersonal Skills #  Behavioral #  Give me an example of a time when you had to deal with a difficult co-worker. How did you handle the situation?
Describe a difficult time you have had dealing with an employee or customer. Why was it difficult? How did you handle it? What was the outcome?
Describe a time when you were instrumental in creating or improving a good relationship with another department within your company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deal With Challenge /Disagreement Among Coworkers</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Deal_with_disagreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Deal_with_disagreement/</guid>
      <description>Q: (Interactive Communication CGC): Deal with challenge/disagreement among coworkers
(CGC, ISO quality officer, 2016.10)
tips: what skills did I have, use?
situation: A coworker raised voice, and commented that I had no clue on ICP analysis.
[Comments: I raised a red flag. 大忌]
 Revisit 2022.05
It is a situational question. Use different approaches when dealing with different personality.
 Scenario #1:
Situation and tasks: Kent Feluschko, training, AECL
Actions: one-on-one discussion, took initiative, Results: problem solved, relationship built, no hidden agenda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work With People From Different Sections</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Work_with_people_from_different_sections/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Work_with_people_from_different_sections/</guid>
      <description>Q: Recall an occasion when you had to work with people from different divisions to accomplish a single goal.
Situation and Tasks: year 2015, our lab at Whiteshell was an accredited lab. There is lab quality management system. I was the author of our quality manual. The coorperate quality officer requested to revise the quality manual for aligning with cooperate quality manual, so our quality manual became a component of quality system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
