<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AECL Case on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/AECL-Case/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AECL Case on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/AECL-Case/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Commitment to Quality</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/03_Commitment_quality_CGC_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/03_Commitment_quality_CGC_2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EC2.1 Sometimes, if we rush, we can make mistakes or overlook a mistake.  Describe a time that you made a mistake and had to act to prevent further impact.  (Maximum 500 words.)
In your response:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe the situation and its complexity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe the mistake you made and how you noticed the error.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe the steps you took to mitigate further impact of the error.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe what the impact would have been if the error wasn&amp;rsquo;t noticed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discuss how often this mistake could happen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please provide the contact information for someone that can corroborate your response.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Meet Objective</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/06_Not_meet_objective_CGC_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/06_Not_meet_objective_CGC_2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EC4.2 Describe a situation where you encountered difficulties and did not meet a work objective.  Describe what happened and why you did not meet your objective.  Describe what you did during the situation.  Describe the impact of your actions and overall outcome.  Explain why you chose this example.  (Maximum 500 words.) [10 marks]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please provide the contact information for someone that can corroborate your response.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage Multiple Projects</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/10_Multiply_projects_management_CGC_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/10_Multiply_projects_management_CGC_2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EA1.2 This position will involve managing multiple people and multiple projects.  Describe a situation at work where you demonstrated your ability to manage simultaneous work tasks that had multiple people relying on the outcomes.  (Maximum 500 words.)  [10 marks]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please provide the contact information for someone that can corroborate your response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In your response, describe:
The techniques or tools you used to manage the tasks.&lt;br&gt;
How you managed expectations of the people relying on the outcomes.
How well the tasks were completed and how you evaluated the quality of the outcomes.
What you would do differently next time.
What you would continue to do next time.
Why you chose this example to demonstrate your competency in planning, organizing, and coordinating.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Established Expectations</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/07-CGC-Senior-Tech/Interview/12_meet_expectactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/07-CGC-Senior-Tech/Interview/12_meet_expectactions/</guid>
      <description>Q: 12. Please talk about a situation that demonstrates your ability and motivation to ensure your performance meets established expectations.
Revisit 2022.08.02
[Situation]
AECL, expectation: review reports in the same day
multitask
[Task]
programming
[Action]
training, coding
[Result]
more accurate, 100% check</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule Your Activities</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/07-CGC-Senior-Tech/Interview/14_schedule_activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/07-CGC-Senior-Tech/Interview/14_schedule_activities/</guid>
      <description>Q: 14. Describe a situation in which you had to schedule your activities to meet a work objective.
Revisit 2022.08.02
[Situation] LifeLabs
investigate chemical hydrolysis approach.
The supply of enzymes used for hydrolyzing steroid conjugates was short a couple of months after I joined LifeLabs. I was requested to investigate alternative materials to replace enzymes. The conventional approach was to use similar enzymes from different suppliers. All we needed to do was to run verification experiments, finding the volume of enzymes we use based on the activity of enzymes of different suppliers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deal With Difficult People</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Difficult_people_mocking_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Difficult_people_mocking_01/</guid>
      <description>Q: what is the most challenging issue?
The person was not up to the task [power hungry, back-stabbing, knew who to do, but procrastinated the work until last minute].
I tried to put the requests on the performance appraisal.
I used to label them difficult people. I saw them as different people now.
really does not matter at all (at the end of the day.)
 Get the job done is complicated, get the job done with empowering people is complex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disagree With Your Supervisor</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Disagree_with_supervisor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Disagree_with_supervisor/</guid>
      <description>Q: What are some of the things you and your supervisor have disagreed on?
Situation #1: in hiring a quality officer
Disagree on:
I: poor qualification
Supervisor: better personality
Consequence: I respected my supervisor. It turned out a good hire.
Situation #2: Safety moment in the meeting
Disagree with safety practice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
