<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Decision-making on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/Decision-making/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Decision-making on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/Decision-making/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Did you Make An Important Decision?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Make_important_decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Make_important_decision/</guid>
      <description>Q: Give me an example of a time you had to make an important decision. How did you make the decision? How does it affect you today?
  Went to a Toastmasters club.
  Took courses on data science on Data Camp.
  Took the job at LifeLabs.
  Decide to stay in the lab, not go to the compliance section.
  Answer these questions in the answer: What motivated me?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make A Decision With Limited Information</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Decision_without_info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Decision_without_info/</guid>
      <description>Q: Tell me about a time when you had to make a decision, but didn’t have all the information you needed.
Sample excellent response:
I had to make a decision recently between two configurations on one of our routers. Time was quickly moving away from me, and I had to have all the equipment back up in a matter of minutes. I chose the configuration that I had the most data on because I knew at least that I could better troubleshoot it if there was a problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a decision Quickly</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Make_quick_decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Make_quick_decision/</guid>
      <description>Q: Give an example of a time in which you had to be relatively quick in coming to a decision.
[collected from 150 interview questions]
Sample excellent response:
This happens often in the IT industry, but one recent example was when we had a core backbone switch die. It died at the worst possible time — during exams — as they always seem to do, and I needed to get it back up and running quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Follow Before Making a Decision</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Steps_of_making_decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Steps_of_making_decision/</guid>
      <description>What steps do you follow to study a problem before making a decision.
[collected from 150 interview questions]
Sample excellent response:
Following standard models for problem-solving and decision-making can be very helpful. Here are the steps and how they helped me solve a problem with a group project:
 Define the problem to be solved and decision to be made. For a project in an introductory management class, the assignment was to report on the corporate structure and financial situation of a couple of companies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
