<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interview on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interview on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Effective Interpersonal Skills</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Interpersonal_skills_healthcanada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Interpersonal_skills_healthcanada/</guid>
      <description>DEFINITION
Works collaboratively with others, readily shares information, knowledge and personal strengths, and seeks to understand and the perspectives of others to achieve common goals.
QUESTIONS
We must often work as a team to get a task done and sometimes the members of that team differ from us in temperament or in the way they work. Tell us about a recent experience in which you were part of team and had to adapt to working with someone despite your differences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ability to set priorities and meet deadlines</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Prioritizing_healthcanada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Prioritizing_healthcanada/</guid>
      <description>[Location: Health_Canada_interview-4, 20:29]
DEFINITION
Organize time, work, and resources to accomplish objectives effectively; focuses personal efforts on achieving results consistent with the organization&amp;rsquo;s objectives.
QUESTIONS
Often/typically, your work day isn&amp;rsquo;t all laid out for you and you need to decide what you&amp;rsquo;ll do first, second, third, etc. Could you tell us about a time when it was especially tricky to manage your time because of competing demands?
 What situation where you working in?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attention to Detail</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Attention_detail_healthcanada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Attention_detail_healthcanada/</guid>
      <description>Location: Health_Canada_interview-3, 1:00:16
DEFINITION
Demonstrates conscientiousness, consistency and thoroughness by verifying work, information, roles and functions.
QUESTIONS
Describe a situation where you did not pay as close attention to the details as you should have.
 What was the consequence of the error? What did you do to resolve the situation? What would you do differently the next time?  RESPONSE
[Situation: LifeLabs] experiments of optimizing SPE.
[Task / Procedure] test 4 SPE columns, 3 washing reagents, and 2 eluting reagents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initiative</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Initiative_healthcanada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Initiative_healthcanada/</guid>
      <description>Location: Health_Canada_interview-3, 1:19:10
DEFINITION
Seeks to actively influence events rather than passively accept the status quo. Originates, develops and carries through activities. Undertakes new work activities without specific direction. Rectifies a situation by taking corrective action rather than placing blame. Strives to design and organize activities to carry them through to completion.
QUESTIONS
Please give an example of a recent idea that you had to improve the way things are done at work or in your community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Respectful of Diversity</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Respectful_diversity_healthCanada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Respectful_diversity_healthCanada/</guid>
      <description>DEFINITION
Demonstrates one&amp;rsquo;s respect for and appreciation of people from various backgrounds and of varying viewpoints. It also involves a commitment to the equitable treatment of all employees by recognizing, acknowledging and valuing individual differences and needs through the principles of acceptance and accommodation.
QUESTIONS
In order to meet the requirements of the lab quality program, your supervisor asks you to check the analytical records of one of your colleagues. You realize that your colleague has made several errors in his record.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking Things Through</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Think_through_healthcanada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Think_through_healthcanada/</guid>
      <description>[Location: Health_Canada_interview-3, 39:39]
DEFINITION
Advise and plan based on analysis of issues and trends, and how these link to the responsibilities, capabilities, and potential of the organization. Scan an ever-changing, complex environment in anticipation of emerging crises and opportunities. Develop well-informed advice and strategies that are sensitive to the various needs of multiple stakeholders and partners, reflect the strategic direction, and position the organization for success.
QUESTIONS Being able to identify and solve problems is an important aspect of being a Chemist II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Values and Ethics</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Value_ethics_healthcanada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Value_ethics_healthcanada/</guid>
      <description>[Location: Health_Canada_interview-4]
DEFINITION
Serve Canadians, ensuring integrity in personal and organizational practices, and respect people and Public Service principles, including democratic, professional, ethical, and people values. Build respectful, diverse and inclusive workplaces where decisions and transactions are transparent and fair.
QUESTIONS
You have been assigned to verify results from another analyst. During your verification, you have noted an error in the assay of several samples related to a specific drug. It appears that the analyst used the wrong data in applying the formula.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
