<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Incorporating Humor Into Speeches and Presentations on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/Incorporating-Humor-Into-Speeches-and-Presentations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Incorporating Humor Into Speeches and Presentations on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/Incorporating-Humor-Into-Speeches-and-Presentations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Funny How Humor Works</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/01_how_humor_works/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/01_how_humor_works/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Funny How Humor Works
As Groucho knew, it&amp;rsquo;s a form of mental exercise that expands our flexibility and stamina
Julius Henry Marx in &#39;Duck Soup,&#39; 1933. He knew &#39;Groucho&#39; was funnier. &amp;ldquo;I just shot an elephant in my pajamas,&amp;rdquo; goes the old Groucho Marx joke. &amp;ldquo;How he got in my pajamas I don&amp;rsquo;t know.&amp;rdquo;
You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard that one before, or something similar. For example, while viewing polling data for the 2008 presidential election on Comedy Central, Stephen Colbert deadpanned, &amp;ldquo;If I&amp;rsquo;m reading this graph correctly…I&amp;rsquo;d be very surprised.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humor 101</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/02_humor_101/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/02_humor_101/</guid>
      <description>If you find yourself avoiding humor out of fear of failing, you may be overlooking one of the most powerful weapons available to you.
Meet Jones. He&amp;rsquo;s giving a progress report on the new project he&amp;rsquo;s managing and, since he wants to add some levity to his presentation, he starts off with a great new joke that landed in his e-mail box last week. But Jones doesn&amp;rsquo;t realize that his &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; joke has in fact been circulating on the Internet for at least six months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering the Laugh</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/03_mastering_the_laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/03_mastering_the_laugh/</guid>
      <description>Mastering the Laugh #  Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, humor is hard! Toastmasters helps us overcome stage fright, speak to strangers and think on our feet. We&amp;rsquo;re adept at speaking to inform, persuading our audiences and touching them with inspirational tales of love and loss. But how do we &amp;ldquo;break a leg&amp;rdquo; (a good thing in comedy parlance) by tickling our audiences&#39; &amp;ldquo;funny bones&amp;rdquo;?
Speeches employing humor are better received; audiences are more receptive when they&amp;rsquo;ve laughed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humor to the Rescue</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/04_humor_to_the_rescue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/04_humor_to_the_rescue/</guid>
      <description>A witty response is good for business.
For a leader who&amp;rsquo;s building social and business relationships, humor is a wonderful tool. People want to associate with leaders who have a positive personality and a sense of humor. When you are skilled at using humor, it increases trust and likeability. It builds, and sometimes even rescues, relationships. It clearly strengthens your leadership skills. As a significant fringe benefit, a sense of humor gives you a better-tuned humor radar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Comfy with Comedy</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/05_getting_comfy_with_comedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/05_getting_comfy_with_comedy/</guid>
      <description>The right amount of well-placed and appropriate humor can make your speech a smashing success!
Using humor effectively can be tricky. We&amp;rsquo;ve all sat through functions where the speaker is a John Cleese wannabe who hardly belongs on Monty Python&amp;rsquo;s Flying Circus. Not to suggest that public speaking must be a laugh fest, but injecting just the right joke at just the right moment into an address can really capture your audience&amp;rsquo;s attention and goodwill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Add Humor to Any Speech</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/06_add_humor_to_speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/06_add_humor_to_speech/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to make people laugh. You&amp;rsquo;ll have more fun, and the listeners will too!
Listeners appreciate a little humor, even in a serious speech. Done incorrectly, humor can be a disaster. Executed correctly, humor lightens the load, eases the burden and releases tension. There are three basic methods for adding humor to a speech: Tell a canned joke, tell an original joke or simply make a wry observation.
Method #1: Canned Jokes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comic Timing - The Pause That Refreshes</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/07_comic_timing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/07_comic_timing/</guid>
      <description>Humor is one of the most effective tools for connecting with an audience. It builds bonds and refreshes the mind. And although the right words can make people laugh, humor is more than just words. As speakers, we learn that the impact of humor is heightened by how you say it, what you do when you say it, and how you use silence&amp;hellip;the pause. The pause adds punch to the punchline!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Tell Jokes</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/08_tell_jokes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/08_tell_jokes/</guid>
      <description>Are you one of those people who always complain, &amp;ldquo;I just can&amp;rsquo;t tell a joke&amp;rdquo;? Sometimes we tell ourselves this, but it is not necessarily true. Being good at telling jokes doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to be a comedian. What it requires is a better understanding of some basics of telling jokes and a little practice. Once you familiarize yourself with these basics, your joke-telling skills will improve.
The four basic rules of jokes are timing, rhythm, rule of threes, and material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweating Out Stand-up Comedy</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/09_sweating_out_stand-up_comedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/09_sweating_out_stand-up_comedy/</guid>
      <description>There is no substitute for stage time.
It is possible to hear yourself sweat. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen instantly. First, you become aware of the metallic hum of the nearby speakers. Then comes the forlorn rattle of ice cubes in cocktail glasses, then the subtle but unmistakably self-conscious clearing of throats. And then comes a terrifying symphony of creaks, groans, squeaks, scrapes and shuffles you never noticed before, all pouring out of that pitiless black void in front of you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving From Toxic to Nourishing Humor</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/10_from_toxic_to_nourishing_humor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/10_from_toxic_to_nourishing_humor/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s the difference between humor that helps and humor that hurts?
Have you ever had someone say to you, &amp;ldquo;I was only kidding? Can&amp;rsquo;t you take a joke?&amp;rdquo; Do you ever feel guilty after laughing at a joke? Have you ever been an evaluator at a club meeting when the speaker used inappropriate humor?
Do you wonder why I am asking these questions? These queries will help us focus on the most important question when it comes to using humor: To tell the difference between constructive and destructive humor, between humor that helps and humor that hurts, between laughing *with* others and laughing *at* others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acceptable Humor: The Mark of a Professional</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/11_acceptable_humor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/11_acceptable_humor/</guid>
      <description>How to navigate the minefield of good and bad taste.
At a recent Table Topics session, our Topicsmaster quoted a news clipping about someone who grafted an ear to his forehead in the name of art. A member responded: &amp;ldquo;We were asked if an ear grafted to the forehead was art. Technically, it&amp;rsquo;s called Forehead Art&amp;hellip;or F-ART. Which gives you my answer to whether or not it&amp;rsquo;s art.&amp;rdquo;
Oops. That joke crossed the invisible line separating appropriate humor from the inappropriate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Tell Tall Tales</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/12_tell_tall_tales/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/04-Humorous-anecdotes-N-quotes/02-Humorous-anecdotes/03-Messages/12_tell_tall_tales/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;We discovered that tall tales work like potato chips - once we started writing, we couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop at just one.&amp;quot;
The announcement was made in July: &amp;ldquo;This year, instead of a humorous speech contest, District 27 will hold its first Tall Tales contest.&amp;rdquo; Everyone in the room responded with an, &amp;ldquo;Oh!&amp;rdquo; and I think we may have achieved a record for the variety of ways to say that word. Some were intrigued, some were enthusiastic&amp;hellip; but most of our members were confused and concerned.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
