<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CGC on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/CGC/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CGC on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/CGC/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stress Management</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Stressful_Aspect_of_the_Role/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Stressful_Aspect_of_the_Role/</guid>
      <description>A: Stress is not a failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Are You The Best Fit For Supervisor?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Why_is_the_best_fit_for_supervisor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Why_is_the_best_fit_for_supervisor/</guid>
      <description>My strength #  My strength: Commitment to team success (1), organization/plan, monitoring, deliver constructive feedback, build up others, build trust in relationship, hold myself accountable for mistakes rather than blame team members.
My experience #  Experience in supervision in unionized environment.
Experience in planning, assigning tasks, monitoring performance.
Experience in motivation,
Misc. #  CGC: Chemist [2022.06]
Chalk River: Dosimetry second head [2016.09]
Koch: Lab manager [2018.06]
  Commitment to team success: run the business as if it is my business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deal With Challenge /Disagreement Among Coworkers</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Deal_with_disagreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Deal_with_disagreement/</guid>
      <description>Q: (Interactive Communication CGC): Deal with challenge/disagreement among coworkers
(CGC, ISO quality officer, 2016.10)
tips: what skills did I have, use?
situation: A coworker raised voice, and commented that I had no clue on ICP analysis.
[Comments: I raised a red flag. 大忌]
 Revisit 2022.05
It is a situational question. Use different approaches when dealing with different personality.
 Scenario #1:
Situation and tasks: Kent Feluschko, training, AECL
Actions: one-on-one discussion, took initiative, Results: problem solved, relationship built, no hidden agenda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lay Off Coworkers Before Due Date</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Lay_off_before_project_due_date/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Lay_off_before_project_due_date/</guid>
      <description>一起做项目的同事在离项目截至日期前三个月被告知裁员，你如何应对？
Revision 2018.10
#1 Teamwork.
#2 Result oriented.
#3 Empathy.   Original 2016.10
(CGC, ISO quality officer, 2016.10)
I did not read the question carefully at the first place. Then I responded as follows:
I would comfort this coworker with compassion, and encourage him/her to be prepared for the bright future.
I could do better with the following response:
it would be a better time to show profession; show integrity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenging Two-way Communication</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Challenging_2_way_communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Challenging_2_way_communication/</guid>
      <description>Give us an example of a time when establishing two-way communication with an individual or group was especially challenging.
listen, understand, communicates openly with them, recognizes their contribution, and gives feedback and encouragement that enhance their job performance, do not take the issue personally. Be assertive
Revision: 2022.05.31 Situation:
Revision: 2018.10.17 Situation: Chantelle. She said that she knew everything about ICP-OES. When I pointed out errors on the spreadsheets or reports, She got offended.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
