<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Critical Thinking on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/Critical-Thinking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Critical Thinking on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/Critical-Thinking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chemical Hydrolysis Approach</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/02-Working-Situations/05-LifeLabs/01_Chemical_hydrolysis_approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/02-Working-Situations/05-LifeLabs/01_Chemical_hydrolysis_approach/</guid>
      <description>The supply of enzymes used for hydrolyzing steroid conjugates was short a couple of months after I joined LifeLabs. I was requested to investigate alternative materials to replace enzymes. The conventional approach was to use similar enzymes from different suppliers. All we needed to do was to run verification experiments, finding the volume of enzymes we use based on the activity of enzymes of different suppliers.
The experiments turned out the enzyme substitute was not acceptable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SPE Optimization</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/02-Working-Situations/05-LifeLabs/02_SPE_optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/02-Working-Situations/05-LifeLabs/02_SPE_optimization/</guid>
      <description>While I investigated three hydrolysis approaches, I encountered a problem cleaning up steroids using a solid-phase extraction (SPE) method at LifeLabs. Some targeted steroids were lost.
I was recommended using this SPE method which was initially developed for the testing of steroids in serum, but I had to make a new method for my application.
Here is what I did:
 I consulted with a medical scientist to analyze the problem&amp;rsquo;s root cause and come up with solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking Things Through</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Think_through_healthcanada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/02-Health-Canada-Chemist/02-Interview/Think_through_healthcanada/</guid>
      <description>[Location: Health_Canada_interview-3, 39:39]
DEFINITION
Advise and plan based on analysis of issues and trends, and how these link to the responsibilities, capabilities, and potential of the organization. Scan an ever-changing, complex environment in anticipation of emerging crises and opportunities. Develop well-informed advice and strategies that are sensitive to the various needs of multiple stakeholders and partners, reflect the strategic direction, and position the organization for success.
QUESTIONS Being able to identify and solve problems is an important aspect of being a Chemist II.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
