<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interview Tips on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/Interview-Tips/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interview Tips on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/Interview-Tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Have you ever worked on a project that was a failure?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Project_failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Project_failure/</guid>
      <description>Hint: Life is full of ups and down, successes and failures. The role-coaster ride goes on for most of us, basically since the day we are born until the day we die. In some periods of life successes may prevail and we may feel like standing on the top of the world. But sooner or later a huge setback arrives, teaching us a lesson of humility and acceptance.
Recruiters and hiring managers know that we learn the most important lessons when things do not go as planed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unfavorable Policy</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Unfavorable_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Unfavorable_policy/</guid>
      <description>CEO, manager, programmer, manual worker – they all have to comply with policies, rules, and laws that govern different sectors of economy, as well as with the internal policies and procedures of an organization they work for.
Not every rule makes sense, and not each procedure is the most effective one. Yet there are higher goals we have to keep in mind–public safety, environment, justice. Once you start your own business, you can set at least some rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Develop a Thick Skin When It Comes to Job Interviews and Rejections</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Interview_rejection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Interview_rejection/</guid>
      <description>A rejection is not easy to take if you take it personally, and it does feel personal. However, many factors go into the final decision. Some of them have nothing to do with you, but with circumstances. For example, someone from within the company got recommended for the same position by a manager from another department. Since that person already knows about the company and its culture and modus operandi, it may save the hiring manager time and cost in getting the internal candidate onboard and getting productive than hiring someone from outside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Supervisor Interview Q&amp;A</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/25_supervisor_interview_QA/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/25_supervisor_interview_QA/</guid>
      <description>What characterize a great supervisor? #  A great supervisor can motivate their subordinates, they go by example, they have good observation skills, and they can utilize the strengths of the people they lead in their teams. Alternatively you can say that great supervisor maintains the highest possible productivity and motivation of the team (or of each team member), and helps the company to achieve their goals on an ongoing basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deal with a Difficult Employee</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Difficult_people_tip_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Difficult_people_tip_01/</guid>
      <description>Q: Tell me about a time you had to deal with a difficult employee
Difficult people are an inevitable part of life – and as a manager, your ability to deal with them in the right way is extra important.
You’d be surprised at the amount of useful skills you can demonstrate in answering this question well – as long as you adequately describe the resolution (and its impact), as well as the problem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
