<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gordon Foundation on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/Gordon-Foundation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gordon Foundation on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/Gordon-Foundation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What do you know about Our Business?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/03-Gordon-Foundation/01-Interview-Prep/Know_your_business_Gordon_prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/03-Gordon-Foundation/01-Interview-Prep/Know_your_business_Gordon_prep/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Foundation is a charitable organization. Gordon Foundation initiated DataStream program. The goal is to share the data. In order to do that, data must be standardized, verified, to comply with an observation-level data schema (standard) based on WQX standard (It was designed to enable multiple monitoring entities to share results in a common format).
DataStream was first piloted in the Mackenzie Basin with the support and collaboration of the Government of the Northwest Territories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strength and Weakness</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/03-Gordon-Foundation/01-Interview-Prep/Strength_N_Weakness_Gordon_prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/03-Gordon-Foundation/01-Interview-Prep/Strength_N_Weakness_Gordon_prep/</guid>
      <description>Strength: technical savvy.
Weakness:
 there are still lots to learn. Learn programming codes on the job. had few presentation opportunities at work, but practiced the skillset at Toastmasters. syllable missing.
   I have done a self-assessment for data scientists and data analysts.
Strength:
 I am a good listener. I am focused on getting tangible business results with data. no problem of talking in front of a group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Us?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/03-Gordon-Foundation/01-Interview-Prep/Why_US_Gordon_prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/03-Gordon-Foundation/01-Interview-Prep/Why_US_Gordon_prep/</guid>
      <description>) Career perspective: It is an opportunity of career advancement. There are many data. development. in line with my experience. I love to organize data.
)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell me about yourself</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Tell_me_about_yourself_Gordon_prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Tell_me_about_yourself_Gordon_prep/</guid>
      <description>Approach #1: summarize my resume with the focus on their business in mind. high level: 14 years of experience in laboratory analysis for environmental monitoring and drinking water safety, and learned R. My experience helps me understand stakeholder field and communicate stakeholders well.
low level: Data processing, interpretation, and presentation.
 Involvement in the EDMS project at AECL, similar to DataStream&amp;rsquo;s data schema.
) Experience with Ontario environmental data management system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Are You Interested in Applying for This Job?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/Why_interest_in_this_job_Gordon_prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/Why_interest_in_this_job_Gordon_prep/</guid>
      <description>) Point #1: I can do the job. I enjoy in what I am doing.
) Skills and qualifications: I have master degree, work experience in environmental monitoring, proficiency with Excel, proficiency in R. My project report would demonstrate my presentation and communication skills.
)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
