<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Planning, organizing, and coordinating on Mianshi Handbook</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/Planning-organizing-and-coordinating/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Planning, organizing, and coordinating on Mianshi Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/Planning-organizing-and-coordinating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Planning, organizing, and coordinating</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/04_Planning_CGC_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/04_Planning_CGC_2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EC3.1 Describe one of your team&amp;rsquo;s largest or most important projects or activities and how you managed it, from start to finish.  Use a project or activity where others were doing the work, but you were overseeing it.  (Maximum 500 words.) [10 marks]
–	What was the vision for this project/activity?
–	What was the outcome?  How do you know this was the outcome?
–	What was your role in reaching that outcome?
–	Looking back, what would you have done differently?  Why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please provide the contact information for someone that can corroborate your response.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plan Complex Work Tasks</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/09_Multiply_projects_planning_CGC_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/01-Interview-Experience/01-CGC-Chemist_2022/01-Take-Home-Exam/09_Multiply_projects_planning_CGC_2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EA1.1 You have a validated multi-analyte method currently in use on one LC-MS/MS (instrument A).  You need to have a backup method in place on a different LC-MS/MS (instrument B) so that your team has continuous analytical capabilities in case of instrument issues, technician absences, etc.  Developing the method for instrument B, and training a new technician will involve coordination amongst the two technicians, as well as with the team lead for another group that also uses the same two instruments.&lt;br&gt;
Describe in detail the plan you would use to get the backup method operational so that there is always available analytical capability.&lt;br&gt;
Describe why you include certain steps in your plan, as well as your reasons for the order of steps in your plan.  (Maximum 500 words.) [10 marks]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
